https://www.3wstudios.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Contact Us: +1 (850) 878 6663
3W Studios Privacy Policy
3W Studios is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. This Privacy Policy, effective July 1, 2016, explains how 3W Studios collects and uses any information a user (‘user’ or ‘you’) provides us with when you use the website. If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact contact@3wstudios.com.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect personal information from users in a variety of ways. We collect information that users directly give to use, like their name, email address, and phone number,  and when they submit online forms. We use third-party tools like Google Analytics, as well as social media platforms like Facebook and Twitter, to collect and understand data about our online users. For example, information about how users navigate between pages or if they when referred from a social media platform is collected and stored so we can further improve our marketing   and website.
Also, we use cookies to increase the responsiveness of our website and provide better        online experiences for our users. Cookies are small data files that get stored on your computer.   A COOKIE CANNOT GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER OR ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION STORED ON YOUR COMPUTER.
You can decline cookies by modifying your browser settings. To view more information about cookie settings, please visit:
For Google Chrome:http://www.google.com/support/chrome/bin/answer.py?answer=95647
For Mozilla Firefox:http://support.mozilla.com/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies
For Apple Safari 5:http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html
ONLINE ADVERTISING WE USE
We use Google Ad Words Remarketing to advertise to previous users of our site across 3rd party websites and search engines. Ad Words remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the 3W Studios website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. We also use Facebook’s Remarketing to advertise to previous users of our website to display relevant Facebook ads. Any data collected is used by our privacy policy as well as the privacy policies of Google and Facebook.   By continuing to use the 3W Studios website, you are agreeing and accepting the terms of this privacy policy.
You can opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting: www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Request More Information
Please completed the form below and we will be in touch as soon as possible.First Name*Last NameEmail Address*
Phone Number*Questions / CommentsPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle AJAX powered Gravity Forms.
2074 Centre Pointe Blvd Suite 200,
